# Sinan Özata - Full Stack Web Developer

Phone: +90 544 955 55 56 | Email: sinanozata1@gmail.com | Skype: sinanozata\_44

Github: sinanzt Istanbul / Turkey



#### **А**воит

I m a Software Developer. I live in İstanbul. I can describe myself as a multi-hat developer especially focused on web and mobile-based technologies. I have worked as a Full Stack Developer in many projects professionally for about 8 years. I used Laravel, Angular in most of our projects. We have developed mobile applications with Ionic.

We are developing a field sales automation system in my company at the moment. We use Java on the backend and Angular on the frontend for this project. So I use Java for 2 years.

I worked as a manager for many projects and complete a lot of different project. Some projects are below

#### EXPERIENCE

### Bil - Gel Yazılım - Full Stack Developer

#### Nov 2018 – Present

- + We have developed a comprehensive sales automation system. This software includes many different subprojects. It covers different projects such as salesman software, manager software, distributor software. We also developed a mobile application for salesman.
- + The technologies we use:

Backend: PHP - Laravel, Java - Spring Boot / Frontend: Angular, CSS, HTML5 / Database: PostgreSQL and MySQL / Mobile application: Ionic

http://salesart.io (Website)

## **Space Tech - Full Stack Developer**

Nov 2016 - Nov 2018

- + Developed an in-house social media management tool for automating Twitter accounts

  Application Layer: Nodejs, Slimerjs, RabbitMQ, Backend: PHP Laravel, Mysql, Frontend: Angular, Html, Css
- + Developed hybrid mobile applications with the Ionic framework

### Shift Teknoloji - Full Stack Developer

Sept 2015 - Oct 2016

- + Worked on premium video streaming service using technologies which are Laravel, Angularjs, Wowza Media Server, Redis
- Developed website of a government agency (Laravel)
   <a href="http://www.tika.gov.tr/">http://www.tika.gov.tr/</a>

### Bilisim Teknolojileri Ajansi - Full Stack Developer

Jun 2013 - Aug 2015

+ Worked on multi-language CMS, various websites and news software which focused on heavy visitor traffic are created. Mostly developed with; PHP/Laravel, Jquery, Angularjs, HTML5/CSS,

- + Developed website of a news website (Laravel) (RTL) http://www.akhbarturkiya.com
- Developed website of a new website (Laravel)
   <a href="http://www.haber10.com">http://www.haber10.com</a>

#### FREELANCE

#### Socialn.io

+ It is a saas that your social media feed on your website. I worked on front-end and WordPress plugin

### **Eastern Recruitment**

+ I developed a multi-language mobile application to manage service providers and drivers and worked as a team member of the website development process

https://www.ercmureeh.com/?lang=en

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ercmureeh.ercpersonel

### **Kontrol Edelim**

- + It is a startup that checks the accuracy of vehicle and property ads. I developed a CMS to manage their own employees and workflow. Mechanisms for distributing existing tasks to employees under certain conditions and following them. Also, I developed their Android mobile application
  - o API (Laravel)
  - o Mobile App (Ionic Framework)

https://kontroledelim.com

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.kontroledelim.kontroledelim

### **Anesiad**

+ I developed it to add corporate news, projects photo and video gallery. There is also a main site and an unlimited number of sub-sites. Sites have a hierarchy in data management.

https://anesiad.org (Laravel)

https://malatya.anesiad.org (Sub website)

https://anesiad.org/forum-index (Medium scale form platform)

### **Tgs Otogaz**

+ I developed it to add corporate news, projects photo and video gallery.

https://www.tgsotogaz.com (Laravel)

#### Sulax

- + It transforms requests from customers into a specific business and assigns them to relevant officials. The officers follow the works from the mobile application and share the results with the manager by managing the business process from this application.
  - o API (Laravel)
  - o Mobile App (Ionic Framework)

#### **S**KILLS

# **Primary - Daily Experience**

+ PHP, Laravel, Java, Spring Boot, Angular, Javascript / Typescript, Jquery, HTML and CSS, Ionic, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Nodejs, Express Js , Sass

### Secondary - Experienced

+ Hibernate, Maven, Android

# **Experienced Technologies**

+ Nginx, Apache, Mysql, PostgreSQL, Docker, Linux, Redis

#### **EDUCATION**

# Fatih Sultan Mehmet University (Master)

Computer engineering

### İstanbul University (Bachelor's Degree)

Computer and Instructional Technology Teaching